{"data":[{"question":"He was a stranger. I _____ him before.","a":"had never seen","b":"have never seen","c":"had never saw","d":"have never saw","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Past Perfect tense: \n+ Express the idea that something happened\/never happened before a specific time in the past \n+ Structure: S+ had + (ever\/never...)+ PP+ (since\/for...)","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"14","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"When l went to see them, they _____ dinner.","a":"had already finished","b":"had already finish","c":"have already finished","d":"are already finish","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Past Perfect tense: \n+Expresses the idea that something occurred before another action in the past:\n Action \"finished\"  happened before action \"went to see\"\n+ Structure: S+ had + (already\/never\/ever) ...+ PP+ (since\/for...)","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"14","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"I _____ such an easy exam.","a":"never took","b":"had never taken","c":"have taken never","d":"had never took","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Past Perfect tense: \n+ Express the idea that something happened\/never happened before a specific time in the past \n+ Structure: S+ had + (ever\/never...)+ PP+ (since\/for...)","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"14","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"I was happy to see her again. I _____ her for a long time.","a":"haven't seen","b":"hadn't seen","c":"haven't see","d":"hadn't see","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Past Perfect tense: \n+ Express the idea that something happened\/never happened before a specific time in the past\n+ Structure: S+ had + (ever\/never...)+ PP+ (since\/for...)","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"14","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"When I arrived the pub was no longer open. It _______ down.","a":"has closed","b":"has close","c":"had close","d":"had closed","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Past Perfect tense: \n+ Expresses the idea that something occurred before another action in the past:\n Action \"closed\" happened before action \"arrived\"\n+ Structure: S+ had + (ever\/never...)+ PP+ (since\/for...)","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"14","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"When I rang he _____.","a":"has already left","b":"had already left","c":"left","d":"is already left","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Past Perfect tense: \n+ Expresses the idea that something occurred before another action in the past:\n Action \"left\" happened before action \"rang\"\n+ Structure: S+ had + (already\/ever\/never...)+ PP+ (since\/for...)","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"14","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"I saw that the ear _____ at the traffic lights.","a":"had stopped","b":"stops","c":"has stopped","d":"stopped","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Past Perfect tense: \n+ Expresses the idea that something occurred before another action in the past: \n + Action \"stopped\" happened before action \"saw\" \n+ Structure: S+ had + (already\/ever\/never...)+ PP+ (since\/for...) ","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"14","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"I fell in the street. I _____ like that before.","a":"have never fallen","b":"have never fell","c":"had never fallen","d":"had never fell","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Past Perfect tense: \n+ Express the idea that something happened\/never happened before a specific time in the past \n+ Structure: S+ had + (ever\/never...)+ PP+ (since\/for...","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"14","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"I didn't recognize my cousin. He _____.","a":"had grown up","b":"has grown up","c":"had grew up","d":"has grew up","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Past Perfect tense: \n+Expresses the idea that something occurred before another action in the past: \n Action \"grown up\" lead to \" didn't recognized \" \n+ Structure: S+ had + (ever\/never...)+ PP+ (since\/for...)","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"14","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"There was a lorry by the house and a car _______ near by.","a":"had stop","b":"had stopped","c":"has stopped","d":"has stop","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Past Perfect tense: \n+Expresses the idea that something occurred before another action in the past:\n When lorry stopped by the house, a car was already there\n+ Structure: S+ had + (ever\/never...)+ PP+ (since\/for...)","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"14","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"}]}